(Penny:)Sheldon?
(Sheldon(doing nothing):)You said to do whatever
feels natural.
(Sheldon(doing nothing):)This feels natural.
(Sheldon(doing nothing):)Certainly more natural
(Sheldon(doing nothing):)than what you're doing.
(Penny:)Come on,
you got to work with me.
(Penny:)We need to get connected
with our bodies.
(Sheldon:)Penny, my body and I have
a relationship
(Sheldon:)that works best
when we maintain a cool,
(Sheldon:)wary distance from each other.
(Sheldon:)All right,
let's just say we've warmed up.
You're the "teacher."
(Penny:)Okay. One of the things
that might help you
(Penny:)in connecting with your students
(Penny:)is being
a little more spontaneous.
(Penny:)So why don't we
try some improvisation?
(Sheldon:)Why not?
It seems like
(Sheldon:)you're improvising
your entire curriculum.
(Penny:)This is all about
listening and responding.
(Sheldon:)Gotcha.
(Penny:)I'm going to create a character
(Penny:)and a situation, and you
just jump in when you feel it.
(Sheldon:)All right.
All right.
(Sheldon:)Action.
(Penny:)Okay, it's not a movie.
(Penny:)It's improv.
So no one calls "action."